자막제작 - NSC 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)
We're ahead of schedule.
That's a first, huh?
You wanna grab some coffee?
No, I gotta get home.
We're meeting the wedding planner.
- I thought that was last night.
- No, last night was the caterer.
Should have taken my advice.
Should have just eloped.
- Yeah, well, it's too late now.
- Now, it's not, man. You can do it.
Hop on a plane tonight,
go to Vegas.
Boom, it's all over.
Rachel's mom would
never speak to me again.
That's the best argument to do it.
I've been trying to get my mother-in-law
to shut up for five years.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, what's this?
What the hell are they doing?
- Hit the brakes!
- I'm trying.
Try the emergency brake!
This is Baker 4.
We're on Vinton and Hillside.
It's a hijacking.
I repeat, we are being hijacked.
They're jamming us.
MONK Season 4 Epi. 15
Mr. Monk Goes to the Dentist
토니 샬롭
(에이드리안 몽크 役)
트레일러 하워드
(나탈리 티거 役)
제이슨 그레이 스탠포드
(랜달 디셔 경위 役)
테드 리바인
(리랜드 스토틀마이어 경감 役)
딕테이션
김철균(kim1047@nate.com)
싱크편집
윤선영(seedyun@nate.com)
한글번역
송연주(kselub@nate.com)
번역수정
홍관호(kwanho_hong@nate.com)
한글교정
임재영(dreamimage@nate.com)
ORIGINAL AIR DATE ON USA: 2006/03/10
We just found the truck.
This been sitting here for three days.
Thanks. And they left most
of the cash.
Yes, sir.
And these are the drivers.
Yeah, the ME said they
put up a fight. I mean...
blood everywhere
like there was a struggle.
Well, good for them.
Maybe they injured one of the bastards.
Let's check the hospitals.
I want a list of all gunshot wounds,
knife wounds. / Yes, sir.
- You okay?
- Oh, toothache.
Wait, is that the same tooth?
I told you to take care of that.
Yeah, I am.
I'm chewing on the other side.
It's fine, I hardly notice it.
You're crying.
Randy, you're no good to me like this.
Go to a dentist.
- I have an appointment Saturday.
- Oh, I get it.
You don't wanna use up
your sick days.
You're saving your sick days for when
you're not feeling sick, is that it?
I'm gonna go talk to Monk.
You make me wanna talk to Monk.
God, I just heard one of those guys
was about to get married.
Randy?
I know, I know, it's heartbreaking.
They were so young.
Sweetie, it's okay to cry.
It means you have a heart.
Here, look at me.
You're a compassionate person.
That's nothing to be ashamed of.
- It hurts.
- I know. I know it hurts.
You don't want anybody to see you?
I understand.
You know what? If anyone says anything,
we'll just say that you, uh... / My tooth, oh...
Yeah, perfect, that you
have a toothache. / Oh, god.
- God, this hurts.
- Okay, I think that's overdoing it.
Oh, please, Jesus,
somebody just shoot me.
Randy, no one's gonna believe that.
There's some oil on the floor.
Is that a clue?
Is that important?
Nah, there's oil on the floor.
I'll call the EPA.
So, do you, uh...
any ideas about the robbery?
Did you notice the back bumper,
how damaged it was? / Yeah.
And these side mirrors are pushed in.
I don't think this
armored car was driven here.
- It wasn't?
- No.
I think it was carried somehow
in the back of a bigger truck.
You see the tire tracks
from a larger vehicle.
You're right.
It was probably an 18-wheeler
about 14 feet wide.
So they brought the armored car here,
they unload it.
How did they get the drivers
out of the cab?
With this.
A piece of rubber tubing.
They drilled the hole here.
In the plexiglas.
They gassed them out.
Randy?
Yes, sir?
Bag this up.
He has a toothache. / Yeah, I know.
He's been bitching about it all week.
- What, it's a real toothache?
- Yeah.
I can't believe you lied to me like that.
Why didn't you just say I have a toothache?
I did, like ten times.
Randy, if you don't take care
of this tooth immediately today,
I'm gonna rip it out myself, understand?
Fine.
What?
Mr. Disher?
- Yeah.
- Oh, good. I'm Terri.
Did you do all your paperwork?
Both sides.
Good boy. / Yeah.
Where's your receptionist?
Oh, our nighttime receptionist quit.
- Couldn't stand the excitement, huh?
- I guess not.
So you're gonna be in room B.
That's between A and C.
Well, what if I get lost?
You want me to draw you a map?
- Yeah, I think I can find it.
- Okay. I'll be right in.
Well, Mr. Disher, I'm Oliver Bloom.
Don't get up. Just kidding.
- You're a lieutenant, am I right?
- Yeah.
I can usually guess within one rank.
I see a lot of cops in here.
We're on the medical plan, you know.
Thanks for seeing me
on such short notice.
Oh, that's not a problem.
We're open late on Tuesdays and Thursdays
in case of emergencies.
Also to keep Terri here off the streets.
- He worries about me.
- I do.
You know what I'm really worried about?
I worry about this bad boy right here.
Your number three molar.
Terri, can I have a light, please?
I want you to open wide,
just try to relax.
A little wider.
Okay, just relax.
Okay, okay.
A little sensitive.
Well, I hope you're not in love
with that tooth, lieutenant,
because I'm afraid it's gonna have to go.
Now, we can either pull it next week,
or we can do it today.
The choice is yours.
Let's do it now.
Okay, Randy, we're gonna
put you under for about 30 minutes.
You're not gonna feel a thing.
As a matter of fact, you're gonna
be back here every week for this.
And if you're a really good boy,
I'm gonna give you a sticker afterwards.
What if I'm a bad boy?
Just breathe.
Breathe normally, relax.
I know it's hard with Terri
standing over you.
Can you hear me?
Just relax, I want you
to take ten deep breaths, okay?
One,
two,
three,
four,
five...
Terri, I'm gonna need that angled
director probe again please.
Angled director probe.
Doctor, wait, I think
he's coming awake again.
Come on.
Hey!
- What are you doing here?
- What did you do with Barry Bonds?
I know he's here somewhere.
What did you do?
I know he's here.
- I know he's here.
- What are you talking about?
- Barry Bonds.
- We don't know any Barry Bonds.
He is worth $13 million.
What did you do with him?
- We're with a patient here.
- Yeah, we have a patient here.
- We're really...
- Listen, Barry Bonds.
Hey, hey.
Hey, cut it out.
I'm a police officer.
Hey, sleeping beauty.
Welcome back.
Are you all right?
Am I all right?
Why wouldn't I be?
There was a man in here.
She has a man in here all the time.
You...
you were fighting.
Well, there was a fight, all right.
Between me and this molar here.
It didn't wanna come out.
There's gonna be some
sensitivity for a few days.
I wrote you a prescription.
This should help with the pain.
Now, don't take more
than one every four hours.
Oh, and I almost forgot.
Your sticker.
Captain, there are no reports
of any stolen trucks.
Well, keep looking.
Widen the net.
Start at Seattle and
work your way south.
Captain, here's a copy
of the updated manifest.
The cash was new, right? / Yes, sir,
it would have been easily traced.
All they took were the negotiable
bank certificates over $10 million.
All right, let's follow the money.
How many fences in the country
could handle a haul like this?
- I'll find out.
- Captain?
Randy, welcome back.
You're working with Patterson
on the bank certificates.
Get me Frank Davis
at the treasury department on the line.
And put a list together of all the fences.
Any fence in the country who's got the balls...
- Captain, do you have a minute?
- Yeah, what's up?
- It's about my dentist, Dr. Bloom?
- Yeah?
I think, um...
- I think he might...
- Did he touch you inappropriately?
What? No, Jesus, no. No.
I think he killed a guy.
- He what?
- It happened.
I think that he, Dr. Bloom
and his assistant Terri?
I mean, I think they murdered someone.
- You saw it?
- Yeah, sort of.
I was sedated.
You were sedated?
Randy, one time, I was under anesthesia.
I thought my moustache was a chipmunk.
I was the Green Lantern once.
It was great.
I didn't wanna wake up.
Look, I was supposed
to be out for 30 minutes.
But I was under for almost two hours.
- Was there a body?
- No.
- Any signs of struggle?
- And who did they kill?
- I don't know.
It was a guy.
Male, caucasian, 5'11", 200 pounds.
They were arguing about Barry Bonds.
And I'm pretty sure that I can ID him.
- The baseball player?
- Yeah.
I think this guy thought
Dr. Bloom kidnapped Barry Bonds.
I mean, they were arguing about
how much Barry Bonds was worth.
Hey, you know, if your dentist played baseball,
you know what team he'd play for?
The Yanks. Get it?
It's not funny.
It's a little funny, Randy.
Look, why don't you, um...
take a walk.
Clear you head.
Here, drop this off at Monk's.
He's waiting for this.
Then take the rest of the day off, okay?
Go to the movies, go to the beach.
Okay? Get out of here.
I'll call you later.
Is this everything? The whole file?
Yeah.
Monk, can I ask you a question?
What do you normally charge?
You know, for someone
who wants to hire you.
I mean, not the department.
A private party.
Like who?
Like me.
Is this about the dentist?
The captain called us. He said you
had a reaction to the anesthesia.
- You were probably hallucinating...
- No, I wasn't hallucinating.
It really happened.
It was as real as you are right now
standing in front of me.
Randy, I'm not standing.
But if you need my help...
you don't have to pay me.
All you have to do is ask.
I mean, you're one of my oldest friends.
I've known you for years.
Thank you. I want you to come back
to the dentist's office with me.
Let me finish.
Unfortunately, at the moment,
I have a lot of things on my plate.
No, you don't.
Well, I have this armored car thing.
I have to read this whole file
that's about 120 pages.
And I just found a typo, by the way.
And I have to replace
the lint filter on my dryer.
Filters do not replace themselves.
- Mr. Monk, can I talk to you for a minute?
- I have to talk to Natalie for a minute.
- Privately?
- What?
In the kitchen?
- Now.
- Okay. / Go.
Mr. Monk, this is Randy we're talking about.
He would do anything for you.
And I would do anything for him
except this, Natalie. I can't do it.
I have a thing about dentists.
- You have a thing about everything.
- That's true,
but dentists are in a separate
category altogether, okay?
I can't even discuss it.
I can't even think about discussing it.
I can't even talk about
thinking about discussing it.
Mr. Monk, everybody's afraid of dentists.
Not like this.
Okay, okay, okay.
How afraid are you?
On a scale of 1 to 10.
10. I am so far beyond 10,
I laugh at your 10s.
I lie awake at night dreaming about 10s.
The chair and the probing and
the drilling and the rinsing.
Okay, Mr. Monk, what do you do
when you get a cavity?
I don't get a cavity.
I don't get cavities.
I brush my teeth 12 times a day
and I floss every 90 minutes.
- So you've never been to a dentist.
- Once, when I was 12.
How'd that go?
Not well.
You know, this is ridiculous.
We're just gonna go there and look around.
You're not a patient.
You're not sitting in the chair.
There's no probing.
There's no drilling.
I'll be with you the whole time.
But I... / No.
He's happy to do it.
Great.
I don't see anything.
It happened in the other room.
Room B.
What do you think?
Psst, Mr. Monk.
I'm pretty sure this is how the Nazis
decorated their bunkers.
Don't look at that.
Look, look, look, look down.
Look at the carpet.
What a beautiful carpet.
- It is a beautiful carpet.
- Right? Is that better?
That is better.
Oh, highlights for children.
Oh, find the hidden picture.
I used to love these.
Where is the egg beater?
It's under the sled.
You're right.
And the umbrella is in the cloud
above the snowman.
And the fish is next to the ice skate.
Okay, how are you doing that?
I read that same issue 35 years ago.
It was in the...
it was in...
the dentist's office.
Natalie, I can't do this.
Yeah, no, no, no, no, no,
you can do this.
You can do this.
You're doing great.
Okay, here, here, here, sit down
and think about something else, okay?
Here, I brought the case file.
Concentrate on this.
Lieutenant. You back for more?
No, no.
Actually, I think
I just left my cell phone...
in the chair in room B.
Oh, well, it's empty now
if you wanna take a look.
Great.
Oh, I'm Natalie, I'm just gonna help him.
He can't ever find anything.
I'm gonna be right back.
I'm gonna be right here. Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
Okay, I was in the chair.
And they were fighting over there.
Okay, well, I don't see anything.
He bought new equipment.
He bought new equipment to replace
the stuff that got broken during the fight.
Maybe.
- What's that?
- It's a drill.
Don't be afraid.
I'm not afraid.
Mr. Monk, it's okay.
We're gonna go home now.
You can let go.
No, no, we're not going anywhere.
He hasn't seen anything yet.
- I think he's seen enough.
- Is there a problem?
Oh, no, no, I just left
my cell phone in the other room.
Dr. Bloom, this is Adrian Monk.
He's a friend of mine.
The Adrian Monk, the detective?
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Apparently, the pleasure's all mine.
No, he just has a little
thing about dentists.
You know what?
It happens to me all the time.
I don't take it personally.
Let me help you with that.
Oh, are you working
on the armored car case?
I've been reading about it.
I'm a bit of a true crime aficionado.
I'm sorry, that's just classified.
Well, you got a couple of hobbies then, huh?
True crime and baseball.
Baseball?
Well, yeah, I'm sure I heard you guys
talking about Barry Bonds yesterday.
Well, you know what?
People hear a lot of crazy things
when they're under sedation.
They say a lot of crazy things too.
I should write a book, really.
Yes, sir, I understand.
Okay, we're on our way.
We gotta go, that was the captain.
- Oh, we gotta go.
- Okay.
Take care.
A couple of fishermen just found him.
These two bruises, ten inches apart.
There's another set of bruises
exactly ten inches apart.
Yeah, what caused that?
Well, it must be something
ten inches apart. / Thanks a lot.
Well, what do you got?
You said it was important.
I found this in his trousers.
It was in his pants cuff.
It's plexiglas.
- It's gotta be one of the hijackers.
- He drilled the hole.
So who is he?
Turn him over.
- I don't recognize him, do you?
- No.
Oh, my god.
That's the guy.
That's the guy from the dentist's office.
Randy, I told you to
take some time off. / No, no.
Captain, that's the guy.
I told you I could ID him.
And that is definitely the guy.
What, this is the guy that your dentist killed
along with his hygienist? / That's right.
This the guy that they killed in front of you
while you were in the chair. / That's right.
All right, because Dr. Bloom
kidnapped Barry Bonds,
and they were arguing
about the ransom money, right?
Yeah, what, is that so crazy?
What the hell are you laughing at, Peterson?
I'm not crazy. / Okay, nobody said
you were crazy, Randy.
Out loud. / While you were there you
should've had them put some wisdom teeth in.
Hey, you can't even spell
wisdom teeth, Downey.
- All right, look, Natalie.
- What?
You and Monk were there, right?
Did you notice anything?
No, I wasn't really on my game.
I have this thing about dentists.
Kroger calls it a supermegaphobia.
If germs are here and snakes are here,
the dentists are...
You see that branch up there?
The second one from the top?
The one above that one.
Captain, are you going to
investigate this or not?
Randy, you were sedated.
You couldn't have seen anything.
Fine, I quit.
- You what?
- No, I quit.
I'm sick and tired of being treated
like the village idiot.
- Here's my gun and my badge.
- Randy, come on.
I'm not a joke.
I'm not here to entertain you.
I'm a homicide detective.
Randy, don't be ridiculous.
Take it.
Randy.
Captain, they just ID'ed the body.
Are you ready for this?
It's Denny Jardeen.
- Ooh, I know that name.
- Yeah, he's an ex-cop.
Worked the Mission District.
He was bad news.
He was charged five times.
Excessive force, conduct unbecoming.
Took an early retirement four years ago.
Thanks.
- What's he doing?
- Flossing.
He's determined never to
go back to a dentist again.
- Uh, just pretend I'm not here.
- Monk, cut it out, I mean it.
This is a floss-free zone.
- Since when?
- Since right now.
Cut it out.
- What's this?
- That's nothing.
Background check Oliver Bloom.
You're checking out the dentist?
Yeah, I figured it couldn't hurt
to check him out.
You're doing this for Randy, aren't you?
Why don't you just call him?
Because he quit.
Randy is an adult.
He made a decision and I respect it.
You miss him, I can tell.
Look, Natalie, it's not like
we were going steady, okay?
We worked together.
He was just another cop.
That is not true.
You're right, it's not true.
He's not just another cop,
he was the single most annoying
human being to ever wear a badge.
Present company excepted.
Okay, you guys,
let's try this new one.
I printed up some lyric sheets.
Why do we need lyric sheets?
You're the only one singing.
Just so you can follow along.
So you know what it's about.
- We're making a statement.
- We are?
Okay, let's do it, from the top.
A five, six, seven, eight.
5, 6, 7, 8
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What was that?
- Counting off.
- Five, six, seven, eight?
- 5, 6, 7, 8?
- That's for dancing.
- No, it's not.
You're supposed to go,
"one, two, three, four."
Come on, what's the difference?
It's rock 'n roll, man.
Let's do that blues song
we used to do.
Guys.
Guys, guys, guys!
Hey, guys, guys, why don't we just
stick to the original material, okay?
I mean, that's what the people wanna hear.
What people? Randy,
we're in my stepfather's garage.
Well, Aaron, there might
be people one day.
I mean, touring, record deal?
Come on, guys, wasn't that the dream?
Maybe 17 years ago in 12th grade?
Well, you know what?
I still believe in the dream.
I mean, I believe in
the Randy Disher project.
- Come on, I quit my job for this.
- Big mistake.
All right, let's just do it, okay?
From the top.
If you say "five, six,
seven, eight" again, I quit.
I'm just telling you.
That's good. You know what?
Do you wanna be the lead singer?
Excuse me.
Can I talk to Mick Jagger for a second?
Yeah, sure.
All right, guys, take a break, huh?
Oh, it's a really good job
so far, though. Really good.
- How's it going?
- It's good.
It's great. I mean, I should
have done this years ago.
Yeah, it's pretty exciting.
Um, you gotta send me a T-shirt
or a hat or something.
Or whatever.
Um, listen, I thought you might be interested.
We caught a break on the armored car thing.
We identified the body.
Guy's name is Denny Jardeen.
He's an ex-cop.
He's got a cousin who's done some time
who works for a trucking company.
So we're gonna go pick him up.
I thought you'd like to come along.
Why?
I mean, I'm not a cop anymore, Leland.
Captain.
Look at my notebook.
No more witness statements.
Just lyrics and song ideas now.
- You're writing songs?
- Yeah, I wrote 17 last night.
I'm on fire.
I'm sure you are.
Uh, I also wanted to apologize
about the dentist.
It's just that over the years
you've had...
- so many unique theories.
- I wasn't hallucinating.
Randy, I checked Dr. Bloom out
myself on my own time.
The guy is clean.
He's got no priors.
He's never been in trouble.
I just wanted you to know
that I took you seriously.
The fact is...
I miss you, I need you.
Well, it's too late.
I've moved on.
I mean, the band's my life now.
You're more than welcome to come
and have a listen if you want.
Come on in, be my guest.
Have a seat.
Okay.
How you doing?
Hey.
I should warn you,
you might not like what you hear.
It's pretty powerful stuff.
You might not be able to handle it.
All right, let's rock it out.
From the top.
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
♪ I'm tired of sucking up ♪
♪ and I'm tired of sucking up
and working for the man ♪
♪ keeping people down
'cause the law says I can ♪
♪ cuff my brothers and sisters
that's not the way to be ♪
♪ but honey those days are gone ♪
♪ 'cause baby I am free ♪
♪ I don't need a badge
to tell me wrong from right ♪
to tell me day from night ♪
♪ I don't need a badge
because my eyes can see ♪
'cause baby I am free ♪
All right, that was good.
That wasn't too bad.
That was great.
Okay, now, before you even
knock on the door,
I want you to douse this handkerchief
with the chloroform.
Just like this, okay?
20 ccs, and make sure
he really inhales it.
I don't know about this.
Well, we have to do it,
there's no choice.
No, no, I know.
I mean, I don't know if 20 ccs is enough.
How do you know he's gonna talk?
Did you see him?
He couldn't even shake my hand.
He was a mess. / Yeah.
You get Adrian Monk in here,
and I'll make him talk.
Neal, your fingerprints were all over
the warehouse and on the armored car.
You could hire the best lawyer in the city.
It's not gonna make those
fingerprints disappear.
It is all over and you know it.
Okay, I was there.
But I didn't do the two guards, man.
- I tried to stop him.
- Stop who?
Denny.
Denny Jardeen.
One of the guards fought back and he
went postal, man. And started shooting.
Where's the money, Neal?
Denny's got it.
He's keeping it in a shed back behind
his place until we all split it up.
I got some bad news for you, Neal.
Denny is dead.
Denny? / And there's no money
in that little tool shed.
We've already ripped it apart.
Now that's impossible.
Looks like somebody in your
little sewing circle got greedy.
You can't trust anybody
these days, can you?
Oh, Mr. Monk.
I know it's late.
Can I come in?
Of course, of course.
Thank you.
What, what is it?
Lieutenant Disher was right.
Dr. Bloom killed a man two days ago.
And I don't even know who it was.
I mean, I'd never seen him
before or anything.
- I just don't know where else to go.
- Yeah.
Yeah, are you gonna be crying a lot?
Maybe you wanna lean over the sink.
No, no, I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
I'm just scared to death.
- Yeah, I'll call the captain, right?
- No!
No, Dr. Bloom would kill me.
You can't.
Oh, it's okay.
The police will protect you.
Oh, what is that?
- What, what?
- I don't know.
- What is it?
- I don't, it's right...
it's a something on your face.
Like a smudge.
Smudge. / Yeah.
No. No, you're not getting it.
It's right there.
- Did I get it?
- No.
Here, I'll do it.
Hold on. Okay.
Did you get it?
- No?
- No, it's right there.
Chloroform.
You're drugging me.
Just relax.
Did you get it?
Did I get it?
Did I get it.
- Natalie!
- Captain, is Mr. Monk here?
What would Monk be doing here?
I don't even know what I'm doing here.
I called his house to read him
tomorrow's weather report like I always do,
but he didn't answer.
So I go over there, the door's open.
The light's on, but he's not home.
The door was open?
Thank you for waiting.
The doctor will be right with you.
There's no rush.
Why are you doing this?
Please.
What are you gonna do?
I didn't really have a smudge, did I?
You should be flattered.
The doctor doesn't usually
come in this late.
Especially for new patients.
That tooth.
The roots are about
ten inches apart, aren't they?
If you say so.
I get it now.
I know what happened.
The drivers fought back
during the hijacking.
Denny Jardeen got hit in the face.
He must have knocked a tooth loose.
So Jardeen came here to get
his tooth fixed. Makes sense.
He's an ex-cop,
and you're on the medical plan.
He must have talked in his sleep.
Dr. Bloom said a lot of patients do.
He told you everything.
About the robbery,
where they hid the money,
it must have been like
winning the lottery.
If you say so.
That night, you went to Jardeen's house,
found the money, figured it was safe.
That he'd never remember
telling you anything.
But you were wrong.
He did remember.
Or maybe, when the money went missing,
he just figured it out.
He came back here Tuesday night
while you were working on Randy.
Randy witnessed the whole thing,
sort of.
He was right about everything,
wasn't he?
If you say so.
Hello, again, Mr. Monk.
Is it true that you've only
been to the dentist once before? / Yeah.
I gather it wasn't a good experience.
Well, this'll be much worse.
I'm...
I'm a police officer.
Oh, I know that.
That's precisely why you're here.
You see, Terri and I, we have...
some merchandise we'd like to sell.
Open, open, open.
Some bank certificates.
Now, there's a man in Chicago named
Mr. Cronin who would like to buy them.
But we're afraid of approaching him.
Because we don't know
if he's being watched by the police.
So my question is...
is Mr. Cronin under surveillance?
I don't know.
Have you ever seen
the movie 'Marathon man', Mr. Monk?
No, is it good?
Let's watch it.
Let's, let's watch it now.
I'm not much of a movie guy,
but I have some time now.
Who's in it?
Who's in that?
You're not gonna watch it,
you're gonna live it.
Is Mr. Cronin under surveillance?
Yes or no.
I don't know.
I wish I did. I really do.
But I don't know.
- Is Mr. Cronin under surveillance?
- No!
- Is he under surveillance?
- Yes. Okay, yes.
Yes. We know...
we know all about it.
You have to be careful.
You should be careful.
Now, I really wish
I could believe you, Mr. Monk.
Your teeth are perfect.
I don't see a single cavity.
Is Mr. Cronin under surveillance?
He's not saying anything.
Pass me the extractor please.
I still don't see what's wrong
with the Randy Disher project.
I never liked that name.
Even in high school.
Okay.
Okay, what about
the Randy Disher experience?
How about severe tire damage?
Okay, how about mellow knights with a K?
I gotta say I'm leaning towards
the Randy Disher experience.
How about this?
I'm gonna open up a newspaper
and the first word I see...
that's our name.
Baghdad.
That's good actually.
I kind of like that.
- Baghdad.
- Let me see that.
$13 million in bearer bonds stolen.
Bearer bonds. Barry Bonds.
Not Barry bonds.
They were saying bearer bonds!
All right!
All right, okay! Wait, wait.
Your hands are so dirty.
- Excuse me?
- Could you...
you gotta wash your hands first.
Please.
- You want me to wash my hands.
- Please.
- I'm not gonna wash my hands, okay?
I'm not washing my hands.
Okay, now, just hold still.
We're not animals, here, right?
Please, I'm asking you.
I'm asking you.
- He did wash his hands in Marathon man.
- Don't give me "In Marathon Man."
I'm not gonna wash my hand when
I'm torturing him. / It'll take,
it'll take five seconds, please.
I'm asking you!
Look into your heart. For god.
For the love of god.
For all that's holy.
Look into your heart.
- Look into your heart.
- I'll wash my damn hands, okay?
Look, the lights are on.
No! No, not the wrong soap.
- You gotta use the anti-bacterial soap!
- Give me the drill. / Not the wrong soap!
All right, this is enough, already.
Just give me the drill.
Not that soap.
Drop the drill!
Step away from the chair!
- Don't move, Natalie. Stay there.
- Easy, you too.
Get over here.
Down. Down on your knees now.
Both of you.
You okay?
- I don't have my cuffs.
- Here.
- Give me your hands.
- Mr. Monk, it's okay, it's okay.
It's all over.
♪ I don't need a gun
to make me feel strong ♪
♪ I don't need a captain
shoot me down all day long ♪
♪ I don't need your moustache
don't you condescend to me ♪
♪ I don't need nobody
'cause baby I am free ♪
♪ no I don't need nobody
baby I am free ♪
Wow, that had some good energy.
Yeah, a lot of energy.
Let's watch it again sometime.
It doesn't matter.
I mean, the band broke up anyway.
We couldn't agree on anything.
Name, what kind of music to play.
Or whether or not I should shut up.
Come here.
I believe this is yours.
Welcome back, Randy.
Welcome back.
Are you okay?
- Loose tooth.
- Huh?
I betcha that happened
when they knocked him out.
Oh, gosh, you gotta see a dentist.
Nah.
Mr. Monk, there's nothing to be afraid of.
What, I'll be with you the whole time.
What are the odds of
another dentist torturing you?
Let's not talk about it anymore.
자막제작 - NSC 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/tsm)